redbell.com 2012-11-13

# Security & Privacy

**Security & Privacy**

**Your Security and Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us so we have created the following Privacy and Security Policy. This Privacy and Security Policy is governed by our Terms and Conditions. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy and Security Policy, which will be included on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy and Security Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. 

**Collection of Information/What Information We Collect**  
**Redbell** collects information from its users when they register to gain access to our services or at other specific instances when they are requested to provide us with their personal & business information. During registration, we ask the users for their name, email address, business information and other personal details. _We store information that we collect through registration, cookies and log files._ Once a user registers, he/she is no longer anonymous to **Redbell**. _Personally identifiable information is used by Redbell in order to provide tailored services and to improve the content of the site for you._

When you are on our network and are asked for personal information, you are sharing the information with **Redbell** alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Promotions that run on our network may be sponsored by companies other than **Redbell** or may be co-sponsored by **Redbell** and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. However, you can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared.

We also gather usage statistics such as pages viewed, number of unique visitors, browser software, your IP address, screen resolution etc. for analysis that helps us provide you improved user experience and services.

**Sharing of Information/Who We Share Your Information With**  
_For **Redbell** users, it is necessary to share your order information with a trusted dealer partner to complete your transaction. The dealer partner do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any purpose other than fulfilling the order and post order service._

As a general rule, **Redbell** will not disclose or share any of the user's personally identifiable information except when **Redbell** has the user's permission or under special circumstances, such as when **Redbell** believes in good faith that the law requires it or as permitted in terms of this policy.

**Redbell** may also disclose account information in special cases when **Redbell** has reasons to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating I **Redbell** 's Terms of Services or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) **Redbell** 's rights or property, other **Redbell** network website users, or if **Redbell** deems it necessary to maintain, service, and improve its products and services. Personal information collected may be transferred and shared in the event of a sale.

**Who We Do Not Share Your Information With**  
_With the exception of dealer partners listed above, we absolutely do NOT share your personally identifiable information (email address, phone number, first or last name, birth date, or any other information) with ANY third-party or partner unless you explicitly request that we do._

**Cookies**  
_From time to time, we may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies certain features of the site may not function properly as a result._ **Updation of Information**  
A user may edit his/her account information and profile by logging onto our website and/or by sending a request to [ customerservice@pr.redbell.com](mailto:customerservice@pr.redbell.com).The requested changes may take up to 30 days to appear online because of verification process and server cache policies.

A user account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in the user not being able to access the network. Residual information will remain within our archive records.

**Protection of information**  
As with all information, **Redbell** does not sell any user's personal information or business information until and unless it is permitted by the user. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding product or service usage on **Redbell** network is provided in an aggregate form only and does not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. 

We request our users to sign out of their **Redbell** account and close their browser window when they have finished their work. This is to ensure that others cannot access their personal or business information and correspondence, if the user shares the computer with someone else or is using a computer in a public place. 

**Redbell** takes necessary steps, within its limits of commercial viability and necessity, to ensure that the user's information is treated securely.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while **Redbell** strives to protect the user's personal & business information, it cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted to **Redbell** and you do so at your own risk. Once **Redbell** receives your transmission, it makes best efforts to ensure its security in its systems. Please keep in mind that whenever you post personal & business information online, that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. 

**Customer Service**  
_**Redbell** will never ask for your login, personally identifiable or billing information in instant messages, or pop-ups. If you witness any of these possible scams, ignore them and inform **Redbell** at **+91 11 43757879**.

For certain high value orders our customer service representative may request some identity verification proofs (such as scanned copies of driving license, PAN Card or any other document that has your name & photograph on it) in an email format. This email will be sent only from [ customerservice@pr.redbell.com](mailto:customerservice@pr.redbell.com) and no other email account. We will never ask for credit card information on email or phone. We take your privacy VERY seriously; if you feel **Redbell** is violating your privacy in any way, please contact at **+91 11 43757879**.

_

**Changes in Security and Privacy Policy**  
The policy may change from time to time so please check periodically.
